Dad, please stop drinking.
Don't ask for a beating!
Dad, Dad, Dad!
Just die!
I'll kill you!
Sir.
Well, hello there, beautiful.
Come here.
Help!
He's trying to hurt me!
Somebody help!
What are you doing?
[Dearest Episode 1]
[8 Years Later]
[Xinggang City, Pacific Coast]
[Wen Group Heiress, Superstar Wen Jianan]
[Owner of Cloudsea Club, Alex]
Good evening, sir!
Wen Jianan.
Superstar Wen Jianan
has announced her marriage tonight
to rising actor Chen Xingye
after three years of dating in secret.
Being a wealthy family's
son-in-law isn't easy.
Whether Chen Xingye quits show business
after the wedding
has become the talk of the town.
[Wen Jianan's Mother, Wen Xin]
Sir.
Mrs. Wen has spent 5.8 million
in the Seaview Suite.
Her card was frozen,
so the transaction was declined.
What a joke.
You think I can't afford this?
Listen up.
Open your most exclusive suite,
the Cloudview Suite.
And
get your boss, Alex,
down here.
And not just him.
Even if you bring
all seven of the top men here,
I can still afford this bill.
She wants me, huh?
Good. I've been curious
about the Wen family.
Let's go meet
the Wen family matriarch.
Alex.
It's not easy to get a minute with you.
I had to book the Cloudview Suite
just to see you.
And now, who would've thought?
A measly 5-million bill
is all it took to get you out.
Had I known, I'd have caused
a little more trouble sooner.
Mrs. Wen, you certainly have
a sense of humor.
We made sure
to capture everything
on the security footage.
So what?
The Wen family...
I trust you've enjoyed your evening.
But I guess you don't know this yet.
Your daughter just announced
her May wedding.
Now picture tomorrow's headline:
Wen Group matriarch,
superstar Wen Jianan's mother,
racks up a tab at the Cloudsea
and gets the police involved.
That would certainly
upstage the bride and groom, wouldn't it?
The Cloudsea will give you
the respect you deserve.
But even Mr. Wen has to give
Police Commissioner Chen his due.
Hello?
Wen Jianan.
Bring money to the Cloudsea. Now!
Or I promise you,
your wedding is off.
I already told you.
If you need something,
contact my manager, Shang Yu.
Leave me alone.
What a great mom.
Shang Yu.
My mom owes money at the Cloudsea.
Go pay it.
And clean up the mess.
I don't want this getting out.
Use my personal account.
I'm going to my parents'
for my childhood photos.
We need them for the wedding.
Okay.
[He Mu, matrilocal husband
of the Wen family]
The police.
I need to call the police.
Call the police...
Good. Alright.
It's all taken care of.
The Cloudsea bill. Jianan's accident.
A fatal crash
occurred early this morning
on a mountain road outside the city.
A man driving a supercar
struck and killed a 48-year-old woman.
He lost control of the vehicle
and died at the scene.
Police identified him as Jie,
a server at the city's renowned luxury club,
the Cloudsea Club.
The cause of death was reportedly
a fatal drug overdose.
Recently,
intimate photos of top star
Wen Jianan were leaked.
[Top Star Wen Jianan's Scandal Photos Leak;
Fiancé Calls Off Engagement]
The scandal has caused an uproar.
Her fiancé, Chen Xingye,
issued a statement through his agency
claiming he knew nothing about the photos
and calling off the engagement.
Wen Jianan has suspended
all public appearances
and disappeared from the public eye.
All of her unreleased dramas
have been confirmed to be recast,
and brands are terminating
their endorsement deals.
Her career is worth nothing now.
Why?
[Morgue]
Mom...
I'll make them pay.
Sir, we know who did it.
Wen Jianan was driving
that night.
She killed your mother.
Jie was serving Wen Xin
at the club that night.
He Mu, their live-in son-in-law,
blamed him,
had him taken away,
and made him take the fall.
Jie was their perfect scapegoat.
We'll kill Wen Jianan right now
and make her pay for your mom and Jie!
Kill her?
That'd be letting them off too easy.
Letting Wen Jianan
and her entire family off too easy.
My mother's life
and Jie's life.
To them,
those lives were just problems
money and power could erase.
Death is the easy way out.
I'll take everything from them.
Everything they love.
And then,
we'll all burn in hell together.